[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is Yumbilla Falls, the fifth-tallest waterfall on the planet, located?", "correct_answer": "Peru", "incorrect_answers": ["Chile", "Thailand", "Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alaska, Texas and California are the three largest states in the USA. Which are the next two largest states?", "correct_answer": "Montana and New Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["Georgia and Iowa", "Wyoming and Iowa", "Montana and Georgia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What composer provided the musical score for all the Man With No Name movies?", "correct_answer": "Ennio Morricone", "incorrect_answers": ["Victor Borga", "Bob Fosse", "Irving Berlin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Ghost, when Molly would say I Love You what would Sam always say in return?", "correct_answer": "Ditto", "incorrect_answers": ["Me too", "Same here", "I love you too"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ashanti plays Betty in Resident Evil: Extinction.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saltiness is a taste sensation produced most strongly by which of the following chemical compounds?", "correct_answer": "Sodium chloride", "incorrect_answers": ["Cesium", "Potassium chloride", "Rubidium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year and season did John and Tom kill Nokes in the movie Sleepers?", "correct_answer": "Fall 1981", "incorrect_answers": ["Summer 1982", "Summer 1981", "Fall 1982"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the fictional hotel that delinquents are sent to clean up in the 2006 movie See No Evil?", "correct_answer": "Blackwell", "incorrect_answers": ["Yorktown", "Holsten", "Seville"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Scream did Matthew Lillard (Stu) ad-lib some of his lines?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In terms of A.U. (Astronomical Units), how far is the Sun from the Earth?", "correct_answer": "1", "incorrect_answers": [".92", "93 million", "93"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that root beer comes in two forms: alcoholic and soft drink?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the popular Thai hot sauce Sriracha named after?", "correct_answer": "A town", "incorrect_answers": ["A goddess", "A herb", "A dance"]}]